weather-guru.net 2018-05-14

# SearchFort PRIVACY POLICY

**SearchFort PRIVACY POLICY**

We at Weather Guru take your privacy seriously. This document contains Weather Guru's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Weather Guru receives, collects and uses information in connection with Weather Guru (the "Site").

**Collection and Use of Information**

Weather Guru does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail addresses, gender, age, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information").

However, if a user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters or service related announcements, Weather Guru may request that a the user provide an e-mail address. In this case, by providing their e-mail address to Weather Guru, such user explicitly authorizes Weather Guru to send the user communications.

Weather Guru may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at Weather Guru's Site.

Like many Internet sites, Weather Guru uses Cookies to be able to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. Weather Guru's use of cookies is in not linked to any Personal Information.

Weather Guru may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type and version, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits.

Weather Guru collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, ongoing research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Weather Guru will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

Weather Guru does not rent, sell, or share any information about you with any third-parties.

However, Weather Guru may disclose your Personal Information if Weather Guru believes such action is necessary to:

  * (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Weather Guru;
  * (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Weather Guru (including the enforcement of our agreements); or
  * (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Weather Guru services or members of the public.

**Security and Protection of Personal Information**

Weather Guru takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access.

Although Weather Guru cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Weather Guru implements physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. For example, Personal Information is protected by secured computer networks and access to the Personal Information is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

**Business Transitions**

In the event that Weather Guru goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred in the transaction.

Weather Guru will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Weather Guru may have. This notice will be posted prior to such transfer.

**Updates and Changes to this Privacy Policy**

From time to time, Weather Guru may revise this Policy. Weather Guru will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Weather Guru collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

**How To Contact Us**

For any queries regarding this Policy, please contact us at:

**E-mail:** [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b2d4d7d7d6d0d3d1d9f2c5d7d3c6dad7c09fd5c7c0c79cdcd7c6)
